## Serhat Levent Yavaş

Kayseri, Turkey



serhatleventyavas@gmail.com



05531873760



linkedin.com/in/serhatleventyavas

#### **Summary**

Mobile Developer with 6 years of Java and 5 years of Native Android Developing and 4 years of Native iOS development, UI, and UX design.

Also, I have knowledge of Backend development. I can develop projects with NodeJS and Net Core.

Currently, I am interested in such as Docker, Net Core technologies.

#### **Experience**

## 

Hubtic

May 2021 - Present (5 months +)

#### LY Founder

Leva Yazılım

Jul 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year 2 months)

### Geleceği Yazan Kadınlar Projesinde Gönüllü Eğitmen

Turkcell

Apr 2017 - Aug 2021 (4 years 5 months)

### Software Developer

Procurfy

Jul 2019 - Jul 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Procurfy develops cloud-based solutions, with the goal of simplifying purchasing in strategic and operational aspects, making it possible for everyone to achieve savings and carry out purchasing processes. e-Procurement, e-RFQ, e-Auction, e-BANF

Working as a Backend Developer

### Full Stack Developer

Aug 2015 - Jul 2020 (5 years) Mobile Development Backend Development Frontend Development



Voicity

Jun 2017 - May 2019 (2 years) Sadece kulaklığınla şehri keşfetmek ister misin ?

Seyahat ettiğin her şehirde, çevrendeki yerlerin hikayesini gezginlerden ücretsiz dinle, şehri özgürce keşfet. Gezginler tarafından paylaşılan binlerce Voi ile, rotalara ve turlara bağımlı kalmadan, şehri özgürce keşfet.

### Android & NodeJs Developer

ProSpective Mobile App Studio - Yazılım Geliştirme Firması Nov 2018 - Apr 2019 (6 months)

#### SSD Android Developer

SBD NetSolutions Nov 2018 - Jan 2019 (3 months)

#### Android Developer

ProSpective Mobile App Studio - Yazılım Geliştirme Firması Sep 2016 - Dec 2016 (4 months)

## Stajyer

Kayseri Büyükşehir Belediyesi Su ve Kanalizasyon İdaresi Jun 2015 - Jul 2015 (2 months) Bilgi İşlem Departmanında çalıştım. Bilgisayar ve ağ bağlantı sorunları giderdim

#### **Education**

### Erciyes University

Lisans Derecesi, Bilgisayar Mühendisliği 2016 - Present

### Nhi Evran Üniversitesi

Meslek Yüksek Okulu, Bilgisayar Programlama/Programcı, Genel 2014 - 2016

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

Android 101 Başarı Belgesi - Turkcell 16636

# Android 201 Başarı Belgesi - Turkcell 16643

## 💫 Android 301 Başarı Belgesi - Turkcell

2	Android 401	Başarı	Belgesi -	Turkcell
	21150			

- Web Programlama 101 Başarı Belgesi Turkcell 28912
- Web Programlama 201 Başarı Belgesi Turkcell 29204
- Web Programlama 301 Başarı Belgesi Turkcell 29235
- C-1JVVM7F1 Log(n) Academy Data Structure Udemy
- DATAI TEAM Python: Yapay Zeka için Python Programlama(1) Udemy UC-AGALF2VO
- DATAI TEAM Data Science ve Python: Sıfırdan Uzmanlığa Veri Bilimi (2) Udemy
  UC-LKWRNXEC
- Garage Angular 7 Kursu Udemy UC-P0QU8E5Q
- **Unit Test Yazma Sanatı** Udemy UC-TWRUPLWX
- Java Design Patterns and Architecture Udemy
  UC-07XMCSU1
- Swift 4 İle Başlangıçtan İleri Seviyeye Mobil Uygulama Udemy UC-UR326435
- Android Unit Testing and Test Driven Development Udemy UC-ZTVOF10P
- **Dependency Injection in Android with Dagger 2** Udemy

#### UC-G3E2LAKL

- **Microservices Foundations** LinkedIn
- in Docker for Developers LinkedIn
- The Learning Docker LinkedIn
- in Learning TypeScript LinkedIn
- in Learning React.js LinkedIn
- in Learning REST APIs LinkedIn
- in HTTP Essential Training LinkedIn
- Designing RESTful APIs LinkedIn
- API Testing and Validation LinkedIn
- Become a RESTful API Developer LinkedIn
- in Web Security: OAuth and OpenID Connect LinkedIn
- Programming Foundations: Test-Driven Development LinkedIn
- in C# Test Driven Development LinkedIn
- in Learning Entity Framework Core LinkedIn
- in C# Design Patterns: Part 1 LinkedIn
- Swift 5 Essential Training LinkedIn
- Agile Software Development: Refactoring LinkedIn
- Swift 4: Protocol-Oriented Programming LinkedIn

- Programming Foundations: Refactoring Code LinkedIn
- in Learning Node.js LinkedIn
- in Building a Website with Node.js and Express.js LinkedIn
- Programming Foundations: APIs and Web Services LinkedIn
- in Databases for Node.js Developers LinkedIn
- SSL Certificates for Web Developers LinkedIn
- in Git Essential Training: The Basics LinkedIn
- HackerRank Certificate Problem Solving (Basic) HackerRank 0ec5649925f6
- HackerRank Certificate Java (Basic) HackerRank e4e24a529ffd
- HackerRank Rest API (Intermediate) Certificate HackerRank 2f82cba9c6e0
- HackerRank Problem Solving (Intermediate) Certificate HackerRank 6f2efe20a5f9
- Mocking with Moq and xUnit Pluralsight
- Testing .NET Code with xUnit.net: Getting Started Pluralsight

#### Skills

Android Development • iOS Development • NodeJS • Software Development • Object Oriented Design
 • Design Patterns • Scrum • Test Driven Development • Unit Testing • Software Design

#### **Honors & Awards**

Başarı Belgesi - Ahi Evran Üniversitesi Kaman Meslek Yüksekokulu

May 2016

Ahi Evran Üniversitesi Kaman Meslek Yüksekokulu Bilgisayar Teknolojileri Bölümü Birinciliği

Teşekkür Plaketi - Turkcell

### Oct 2017

Geleceği Yazan Kadınlar Projesinde, Android Uygulama Geliştirme eğitmenliği yapmış olmamdan ötürü verilen teşekkür plaketi.